[Theme song]
- [Dark Music]
- [Fast beep sound]
[Jaewon] Professor!
- Blood pressure drops!
- [Gyeongwon] 30 out of 50
[Man 1 speaks in English] Shut up!
[Jangmi gasps in Korean]
Connect directly
[Jaewon] Yes? No, sir.
No, no, no.
[Rose] Oh, if I keep going like this, I’m going to lose my patients.
[Man 1 in English] Shut up!
- [Engine rapid acceleration sound]
- [Urgent music]
- [Jaewon, Jangmi’s surprised sound]
- [Loud gunshot]
[Repeat loud gunshots]
[Scream of the Rose]
[Man in Speaker 2] Lift alert
[The tense music fades]
[Man 2] Lift alert
no firing
[Meaningful music]
This vehicle is permitted to enter the base.
[Walter in speaker] Unit commander
This is a visit from a person who guarantees your identity.
This will probably be a familiar name to most of you.
Many people in Afghanistan
Because I owed him my life.
malak
That's the name
Medics currently awake
In the ward building
hope to welcome him
and he needs
Provide all support
This is an order from a commander.
- [Urgent music]
- [Fast ECG beep sound]
[Medic 1] Malak!
[Kang Hyuk] Help me prepare for the surgery.
[Korean] Okay, one, two, three
Gangster, secure enough blood
yes, i understand
- No. 1, clean up the boat first.
- Yes!
- Start the drap.
- Okay.
[Medic 2 in English]
Shall we assist?
[Kang Hyuk] No, our team will do it.
[Medic 3] How is the situation?
[Medic 4] That person
Is that Malak?
[Sound of door closing]
[Medic 2] Nothing has changed
[The tense music fades]
Suddenly barging in with a patient
It's the same as in Afghanistan
- [Constant ECG beep sound]
- [Heavy music]
[Beep electronic sound]
[Gyeongwon in Korean]
You can start surgery
- [Kang Hyuk] Energy device
- [Rose] Yes
[Jaewon] Contaminated small intestine
Are you going to cut it all?
It looks like 1 meter?
[Kang Hyuk] 2 meters
You have to cut out all the rotten stuff.
That's how you live
[Jaewon’s exhaling sound]
[Walter in English]
How is it going?
[sigh]
I'll live
[Medic] Can’t you see the patient’s condition?
I can see that kid's face
There's no hesitation at all
[Kang Hyuk in Korean] Irrigation
- [Jaewon sighs in relief] For now,
- [Inhaler operating sound]
The source of infection has been cleaned up.
[Kang Hyuk] Except for the stoma.
Let's take a break for the rest of the chapter.
[Jaewon] What should I do with the bullets?
It's dangerous if it remains in your stomach.
[Kanghyuk] I have to find it
[Jaewon] The patient’s condition is
Can you hold on?
[Kanghyuk] There are no bullets in here
It's in there
[Jaewon] In the intestines?
[Kang Hyuk] I can’t do it if I’m not in there.
It has to be there
If the bullets are still in the ship
Captain Lee Hyeon-jong…
I can't survive
Take it out and find it
Because the operating room is contaminated
[Jaewon] I understand
Please come out, please
Ugh, really
[Sound of clattering down]
[Rose's light breathing]
[Kanghyuk] If you’re tired, go out and rest
You had a hard time, it's okay
[Rose] It’s okay, she’s my patient.
[Jaewon’s heavy breathing]
[Jaewon] Oh, huh?
uh?
uh!
I found it
[Sigh of relief]
[Kang Hyuk] The stomach is done.
Now the left arm is being reconstructed.
[Rose] Left arm?
I cut out all the bones, but how...
Because I cut out the rotten stuff.
I need to put a new one in
[Sound of flesh being cut]
[Rose] Bird bones?
[Kanghyuk] Yes
Prepare the artificial bone
[Rose] Yes
[The heavy music fades]
[light breathing]
Teacher Jaewon
[Jaewon] Uh, teacher
No, no, I'm sitting.
How are you feeling?
It's okay
What about the patient?
Patient? ah…
I'm fine, my vital signs are good.
- Yes
- [Rose’s sigh of relief]
[Rose] I'm glad
But how do we work?
Until Captain Lee Hyeon-jong recovers
It will take quite a while
[Jaewon sighs] So,
- I can't get on any plane.
- [Rose Sigh]
[Walter’s laughter]
[Walter’s happy exclamation]
[Walter in English] It’s been a while.
[Kanghyuk] Yes
[Walter] Sit down
[Walter’s laughter]
[Walter’s joyful exclamation]
It reminds me of the old days
- [Walter continues to laugh]
- [Sound of putting down]
used to be with you
The Afghan era was its heyday.
- [Sound of being handed over]
- [Exhaling sound]
Why did you leave?
[Savoring breathing]
Anyway, I only look for people when I need them.
It's still the same
[Kang Hyuk’s bitter mouth sound]
debt to me
I think it's time to pay back
[Walter] Was I in debt?
What do you want?
[Kanghyuk] You know what I want
[Walter] Are you going all the way to Korea?
That's right
[Walter] That…
The pilot's schedule is full.
You know my temper
These aren't the kids who say they'll do it
By calling
tell me
Malak is looking for you.
[Noisy]
- [Rose in Korean] But
- Yes?
[Rose] Where am I?
Is it the military?
[Sound of ketchup being squeezed]
- Here
- [Putting down sound]
Professor Baek's old workplace
Yes?
[Jaewon] Ah!
The professor
He was a mercenary medic.
It's called Blackwings
But this black...
[Small] Blackwings African branch
here in south sudan
Ah…
Captain Lee Hyun-jong was destined to live.
[Jaewon] But here
Fay is
Pay?
They say they don’t hire nurses?
[Welcome sound of roses pouring into the well]
Professor!
[Mercenary in English] Hello, Malak.
[Sound of holding hands]
[Korean] Let’s go if you’re done eating
To Korea
- [Rose] Now?
- uh!
Did you get the air ambulance?
[Magnificent music]
[Jaewon] No
Wow, no
It's better than most intensive care units.
Noisy and
Now, go quickly and get the medicine.
Check the equipment
Oh, that's Gyeongwon.
I'm bringing it
Did I order Gyeongwon to do it?
[The music fades comically]
[Sound of running footsteps]
[The rose sighs] Teacher Park Gyeong-won
Look at me for a second.
Yes, I saw it.
No, don't we have something to talk about?
[Sound of putting it down]
I'll ask you straight forward.
You're a spy, right?
yes
Did the director order it?
[Rose] To the professor
I won't tell you
instead
Emergency surgery for now
I want you to take charge of it.
Of course
- Yes?
- [Bright music]
[Kyungwon] That’s how you do it.
Well, do you have anything else to say?
[Rose] Oh, kid
Wait, wait, wait
What is it
Boy, if you're going to accept it this quickly.
Why did you do that spy thing?
Because someone has to do it
If I don't do it, someone will
Acting like a real spy
You could have done it
Well, if you pass the national exam
To a major trauma center
I tried to apply, but
Trauma centers cannot disappear.
Teacher, aren’t you crazy?
yes
- I'm crazy.
- [Rose's Laughter]
It went so well…
Please take care of me in the future
[Jaewon] Hey, I… Go, I have to go.
The professor is looking for you. Come quickly.
[Rose] Ah!
Let’s go, Teacher Park Gyeong-won.
[Kyungwon] Yes
- Teacher Park?
- [Gyeongwon’s Sigh]
[laughter]
Hey, is it good? uh?
Hey, hey, are you chewing? uh?
[Captain in English]
On a plane to Seoul, South Korea
Welcome aboard
Hope you have a comfortable trip
I'm preparing the plane for takeoff.
[Reporter in the news in Korean]
The transport plane carrying Captain Lee Hyeon-jong
South Sudan time
Departed at 8 am
Professor Baek Kang-hyuk was dispatched to South Sudan.
Secondary surgery performed locally
Finished safely
using an air ambulance
Decided to move quickly
Coming soon to Seoul Airport
It is reported that it is scheduled to arrive
On the return of Captain Lee Hyun-jong
National attention is focused
- Professor Baek Kang-hyuk, who has proven his skills,
- [click click]
Putting an end to the parachute controversy
At the airport immediately upon arrival
I plan to attend the press conference
[Bright music fades out]
- [Man] ‘Black Wings’
- [Emotional music]
the world's largest
It's a private military company.
I think the surgery was performed there.
I found out that there was an air ambulance too.
I borrowed it from there.
good
It's a story worth selling.
Professor Baek Kang-hyuk
Supported Captain Lee Hyeon-jong's surgery
In private military enterprises
When I worked as a medic
It is said that he received a large amount of compensation.
Most of the money is spent on purchasing medicine for refugees.
They say they donated
sometimes
than one doctor
A pill worth 1,000 won
Because there are times when it is more desperate.
Isn't it?
[Captain speaks in English] Our plane
I'll land soon
[Myunghee in Korean] Yes, you are coming.
Welcome, thank you for your hard work
Captain Hyeonjong Lee
I kept my promise to save you.
[Myunghee] Yes, you mean Doctor Helicopter?
I also made a promise to the professor
I will definitely protect it
First, to our welcome hall.
- This way, first of all, here is the welcome ceremony...
- [Jaewon] Oh, wait a minute.
- [Rose] Professor!
- [Jaewon’s embarrassed voice]
[Noisy]
- [Rose] Please come out
- [Kyungwon] Wait a minute
- [Continuously noisy]
- Now, now, now, now, now, reporters!
[Reporter] Over there, over there
[Kang Hyuk] About the status of Captain Lee Hyeon-jong
I will brief you briefly.
First of all, the most urgent
The bullet lodged in the abdomen was
It was removed cleanly in the second surgery.
Directly damaged area and
Uh, the small intestine that has become necrotic due to infection
Removed some
Captain Hyeonjong Lee
I can go back to the military
First, I have to go check on the patient’s condition.
Please do it later, Minister.
[Myunghee] Ah, yes
- [Continuous barrage of questions]
- Uh...
As you can see
Because patients come first...
[Continues to make noise in the distance]
- [Kang Hyuk] It’s late, let’s hurry up.
- [Emotional music fades out]
[siren sound]
[Myunghee] So
Our Ministry of Health and Welfare also
- Generous support in the future…
- [tire rubbing sound]
What? Who goes where?
[Agnes] Oh, the manager.
at the scene of the fire
right before coming here
Hey, I got a call from you urgently and brought it to you.
Uh, really baby
I think it’s Professor Baek.
- [Siren sound]
- [Interesting Music]
[Noisy]
Ah, I am Baek Kang-hyuk.
I…
[Yurim’s scream]
[heavy music]
Uh, car keys, car keys!
Minister, I need some tea.
Oh, emergency, quickly get the car keys!
[helicopter sound]
[loud siren sound]
- [Firefighter] Hey, patient over there!
- [Man’s groan]
[Sound of door slamming]
[Firefighters continue to shout urgently]
- [Heavy music stops]
- [Siren sound]
[Yurim] Fortunately, there were no injuries
Because it's not big
Let me know if anything goes wrong, okay?
Keep taking deep breaths
Ready to transport, transport
Where, where?
Where does it hurt, where, my shoulder?
[Urgent music]
[loud siren sound]
[Co-Pilot] You can descend.
[People] Here, here!
Please save me, here!
Here, here!
[Sirens sound in the distance]
[Successive honking]
[Jungheon] Go towards the ambulance.
Make sure you get diagnosed, okay?
- [Rescuers] Yes
- [Jungheon] Okay, let’s go.
[Rescuer] Let’s go!
[Kang Hyuk] Team leader
[Jungheon] Professor!
[Kang Hyuk] Are you back on set?
[Jungheon] Yes, there is a welcome ceremony.
Did you get it from the rooftop?
Are you going up again?
[Jungheon] No
The rescue to the rooftop is complete.
I'm going to assist at the fire scene.
Then don't send a helicopter first.
The patient may need to be transported.
[Jungheon] I understand.
[The tense music fades]
Now, relax
Well, what do you think? now…
[Yurim, people's surprised screams]
[Crying] What should I do, really!
Wow, really
[Murmuring sound while straining]
[panting] Oh, thank you...
From children to children, protective gear
I have to do it anyway
Be sure to show off as a novice, Mr.
Professor Baek
Why come now, Mr.
All this time, I was alone...
[Kang Hyuk] Ugh, Mr.
[Continuously noisy]
why
Thank you for your hard work
[Yu-rim continues to cry sadly]
Let's start by classifying
And here at the fire scene
too close
[Yurim] Are you here now?
[Yurim’s continued sad cries]
You know, how do you do it?
- This, this...
- [Kang Hyuk] Uh, team leader.
[Yurim] Oh, I don’t know, I
How do you do this?
[siren sound]
- [Noisy]
- [Reporter 1] When will the briefing be held?
Now, now, now, now, now! Reporters
Hey, you can't do this here!
You need to move out of the way at the entrance...
- [Siren sound]
- [Reporter 2] Oh, the ambulance is coming!
- Ambulance!
- [Reporters keep making noise]
[Sound of pounding]
[Manager Lim] No, no, no!
No, no, no!
[Sound of repeated pounding]
[Rose] Safe and
For rapid transfer
We all have to work together
Once the door opens, Teacher Jaewon
Please lower the bed first.
Agnes too
- Yes
[Kyungwon] What about Teacher Jang Mi?
I have to clear a path from the center.
I'm a specialist in center removal.
Okay, then I'll open it at three.
- Let's go.
- [Jaewon] Yes
one, two, three
- [Manager Lim] No, no, no!
- [A barrage of questions]
[Rose] Get out of the way, get out of the way!
Get out of the way, come out!
[Only emotional music flows]
- [Music stops]
- [Siren sound]
[Yurim] Now, this person…
[Everyone sounds busy]
- Now, be careful, be careful, be careful.
- [Heavy music]
[Jungheon] Professor!
Oxygen cylinder for welding on the 2nd floor
Because there is a company that recharges
I think we need to evacuate first.
If something explodes like this,
Because everyone else is in danger.
First of all, the classification is roughly finished.
Let’s transport the patients first.
yes
- [Megaphone howling]
- All crew members!
Transport the patient first!
[Rescuers] Yes, I understand!
[Jungheon] Now, what you see ahead is
towards temporary shelter
You can move
The crew is as safe as possible
Allows you to move quickly
Patients, it may be difficult, but
Please give me some strength
[Kang Hyuk] Follow me with that sap.
- [Yurim] Okay
- [Kang Hyuk] There is only one person left.
- [Explosion sound]
- [Shocked scream]
[The sound echoes distantly]
[groan]
- [Rough breathing]
- [Dark Music]
Professor Baek!
- Professor Baek
- [Jungheon] It’s dangerous.
[Yurim] Hey, wait a minute.
- [Jungheon] Are you okay?
- [Yurim] Professor Baek!
[Kanghyuk struggles] Starting with the patient
Let’s save the patient first.
[Yurim] Professor Baek!
[Sound becomes clearer]
Don't come
- [Kanghyuk’s labored breathing]
-Are you okay?
[Yu-rim] Professor Baek, uh!
[Kang Hyuk] This patient
Because you must have suffered prayer burns
Start with intubation
- [Yurim] Oh
- [Kang Hyuk] Because you might get dehydrated.
- Add sap.
- [Yurim] Okay, okay, okay
[Kang Hyuk] Team leader, let’s transport him by helicopter.
- [Jungheon] Yes, let’s go.
- [Kanghyuk] Yes
- [Slight moan]
- [Dark music fades]
Team leader
[Jungheon] Yes
Please call the burn surgery professor.
Okay
Why? Not doing it yourself?
Aren't you going into the operating room?
[groan]
[Kang Hyuk] There’s a piece of debris stuck in it.
Because there was no bleeding
Internal organ burns
[Yurim] What?
- [Uneasy music]
- Look, look, look!
Can't you feel me touching you? uh?
[Kanghyuk struggles]
It seems like tissue necrosis is progressing.
- [Sound of grabbing]
- Professor Baek!
Professor Baek!
- [Anxious music fades away]
- [Constant beep sound]
- [Sound of taking off gloves]
- [Rust rustle rustle]
[Rose] Ah, it really came a long way back.
[Jaewon] Of course
It feels like I was filming a movie
Still, it's a happy ending.
[Rose] But now
Let's get ready again
I think patients will come soon.
Oh, that's right, fire.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Wait a minute
Yes, manager.
Yes, I understand…
[uneasy music]
Who?
[shaking breathing]
Ah, teacher, teacher!
- Teacher, what's wrong?
- [Jaewon’s trembling breathing]
A helicopter transfer patient is coming.
the patient
He said he was a professor.
What does that mean?
Professor Baek
You said you were hurt.
[Continuous trembling breathing]
[urgent breathing]
- [Rose] Teacher
- [Jaewon] I have emergency surgery.
- I'm calling the anesthesiologist!
- [Rose] Teacher, what about the housework?
When the professor goes up to the operating table
Who does the housework?
[Heavy breathing]
[panting] Breathing
continue
It's getting faster
- You know what I mean?
- [Yurim] I know, I know
Don't talk too much
I need to stock up on stamina, stamina
Still somehow
I'm holding on
[Rustling rustling sound]
the speed of progress
too fast
[Yurim] Okay, I got it!
I'll give you a sedative first.
[Sound of grabbing]
No way
I have something to tell you No. 1
Not yet…
[Sound of labored breathing]
[Yurim] Now, quickly, quickly, quickly
[Sound of strength]
- One, two, three
- [Jaewon] Professor? Professor
- [Yurim] Come out, come out
- [Doctor] Yes.
[Yurim] Come out, Professor Baek
Come to your senses, come to your senses, come on!
- [Jaewon] What should I do, what should I do?
- Be careful, come on!
- Be careful, lie down here.
- [Jaewon] Professor! professor!
- [Yurim] Lie down, lie down
- [Jaewon] What should I do?
- Hey, go quickly, go quickly.
- [Jaewon] Yes
- [Yurim] Quick, come on.
- [Jaewon] Come on, let’s go.
- Let's go
- [People’s urgent voices]
Wait a minute!
[Kanghyuk’s labored breathing] No. 1
[Jaewon] Yes
You can do it, right?
yes?
Judge
on your own
- Okay?
- Yes, Professor!
- [Crying] Quickly
- [Yurim] Quickly
Let's go, yes!
- [Yurim] We have to keep going, keep going
- [The urgent sound of a rose]
Go straight, keep going
- [Anxious music fades away]
- [Silence flows]
[Only emotional music flows]
[Jaewon] After passing this hallway
There comes a fork in the road
over the past half year
It made me worry so much that I couldn't fly
That crossroads
Now, after passing that corner, I
have to make a decision
Where should I go?
which way
Should I go?
[Rose] Teacher, where should we go?
Hey, let's go from CT, CT first
- [The sound echoes far away]
- [Rose] Teacher Jaewon
[Jaewon] The patient’s condition
CT room for inspection
[Rose] Teacher!
[Yurim] Jaewon!
[Rose] Teacher Jaewon
[Yurim] Jaewon, what are you doing?
[Jaewon] Otherwise
- [Rose] Teacher!
- [Jaewon] Golden time
In order not to miss it, go straight to the operating room.
[Rose] Come to your senses, teacher!
[Jaewon] Judgment
It's up to the surgeon.
- [Sound becomes clearer]
- [Sound of people breathing heavily]
- [Yurim] What are you doing, huh?
- [Rose] Huh?
- [Uneasy music]
- [Yurim] Aren’t you going to CT?
- [Yurim] Uh, Mr. Park
- [Gyeongwon] What happened?
[Yurim] No, heated iron
Abdomen now...
No, how much did it hurt?
[Jaewon’s heavy breathing]
- [Jaewon] I don’t know.
- [Shooting water sound]
It's in the boat, how do you know?
No, something like that
Are you saying something irresponsible?
- [The sound of water stops]
- Don’t you need to see a CT?
[Jaewon] Our surgery
I'll go right in
- Get ready.
- [Brushing sound]
[Kyungwon] How much was stabbed?
I need to know!
If you touch it roughly, you will die.
[Yurim] Yes
Jaewon, Mr. Park has a point.
[Jaewon] No
We're going into surgery right away, Professor.
Trust me
[Kyungwon] Senior
[Jaewon] Hey
Are you a surgeon?
[Jaewon’s heavy breathing]
[Yurim’s heavy breathing]
[Yurim] Come on, come on!
We shouldn't be like this, huh?
I'll try to invite the department heads.
- Everyone just…
- No
I don't have time for that, professor.
I do the housework
[Yurim] I Charm
[Rose] Teacher, shall we go in for disinfection?
[Jaewon] Yes
Please assist me
[Yurim] Teacher Yang!
[sigh]
Please, Professor.
[Yurim’s heavy breathing]
[Yurim] Okay, okay.
First of all, from that piece of metal
Let's get some out.
[Jaewon] I’d like to ask for anesthesia.
I'll just wash my hands and go in.
Mr. Park
us
Let's all do what we're good at
help me just once
[Continuous brushing sound]
[Jaewon] Let’s say we remove the metal.
What about the periphery?
[Jaewon] Judgment
It's up to the surgeon.
[Anxious music fades]
[Jaewon's repeated heavy breathing]
[Heavy music]
[Jaewon] Surgery begins
scalpel
[The heavy music fades]
[Only emotional music flows]
[Kang Hyuk] Am I dead?
[Emotional music fades out]
[Distant phone ringing]
[Busy noise]
[Yurim clears her throat]
[Jaewon] Why…
[Yurim] Are you here?
[Jaewon] Why aren’t you going in?
Oh no
Still, the surgeon
Let's check the status first
[Beep button sound]
- [Kanghyuk sniffs]
- [Automatic door sound]
uh
Professor
Are you okay?
Oh no
[Kang Hyuk] What happened to the patient during the fire?
ah!
Collaborating with burn surgeon Professor Park
You have now been moved to a general hospital room.
The prognosis is also good.
[Kanghyuk’s long breathing sound]
What about other patients while I'm away?
[Jaewon] Uh, recently
There were a lot of traffic accidents
So, orthopedics
There were a lot of patients
With Director Lim of the Emergency Medicine Department
Professor Jeong of Orthopedic Surgery
You helped me a lot
There were no dead patients.
No. 1
Yes, professor
Looking at the surgery records
You just went under the knife without a CT?
Oh, are you a professor?
The professor said so.
Let me judge for myself
That was my judgment
- I need surgery right away...
- So
-What is the criteria for that judgment?
- [Sound of putting down]
The patient's condition
'In severe trauma,
'Textbooks are not important'
‘The patient in front of you is important right now’
The professor said that
How was my condition?
The heat continues
It was spread out.
So the cumulative damage is
I thought there would be
So when time passes
The damage will only accelerate.
After doing this
I thought I might have liver failure.
yes
So I decided
1/3 of the liver
Did you cut it?
It would have been almost like a living liver transplant.
yes, that's right
[Kanghyuk] You bastard
You almost killed me?
You're alive.
That's right
[sigh]
Sorry, Professor.
[Kanghyuk sighs] No
Well done
Teacher Jaewon Yang
- Yes?
- [Bright music]
Professor, professor, I just said my name
What did you say?
[Kanghyuk] Oh
Now I have the right to be called by my name
[Heavy breathing]
- [Muttering] Oh, fuck.
- [Kang Hyuk] What?
[loudly] Fuck!
and!
[Yurim mumbling] What’s wrong? huh?
Professor Baek!
Hold still, let's go in.
But why are you swearing?
- [Rose] Ah!
- [Yurim] Why, why, why!
- [Rose] Professor, oh my, professor…
- [Yurim] What's going on, why!
Oh my, look at this, look at this
- Professor Baek, are you okay? uh?
- [Kanghyuk] Ah, go
[Yurim] Hey, I was really worried.
[Kang Hyuk] Oh, hell, fuck!
[Tsk mouth sound]
Don't talk in the intensive care unit.
Shut up! [groan]
- [Yurim] Oh, be careful, be careful
- [Rose] Oh my
I see you swearing, cursing
To be alive is to be alive, just
Calm down, calm down
[Yurim] Oh my gosh
You had a lot of trouble, just, huh?
- [Kanghyuk’s moans]
- [Rose] I’m still a patient.
- [Yurim] Did you see this?
- [Rose] Professor, are you okay?
- [Yurim] ‘Congratulations, you are alive’
- [Rose] ‘He’s still alive’
- [Rose's Laughter]
- [Kanghyuk] Please everyone get out.
- [Yurim] Okay, shush! fizzle!
- [Kanghyuk’s moans]
[City Noise]
[News Anchor 1] This is the next news.
- [Magnificent music plays]
- Two heroes of South Sudan
Captain Lee Hyeon-jong and
Professor Baek Kang-hyuk’s actions
It's a hot topic every day
In particular, it is necessary to introduce doctor helicopters.
An interview with Professor Baek Kang-hyuk
It's causing a big stir.
Professor Baek’s sincere appeal
There is also a growing public response.
At the major trauma center
Every minute and every second
Crossing the diagonal line
A helicopter is essential
Nevertheless, Doctor Helicopter
The only thing that cannot be introduced is
Because of money
The era of being stingy with life
It must end
Please everyone
At the end of that era
Please join us
[News Anchor 1] Present
To protect golden time
Doctor helicopters should be introduced
Professor Baek Kang-hyuk's
As if answering an earnest request
Various civic groups
Introduction of doctor helicopter
issued a statement of support
National interest also
It's rising significantly
[News Anchor 2]
The government plans to
Doctor helicopter distribution nationwide
He declared that he would expand
[Myunghee in the video]
As a government department, we will do our best
I promise to the people
Severe trauma at the level of developed countries
To build a medical system
The first step begins
I wonder if
- Arousing anticipation
- [News sound quiets down]
[Woman] Honey, you have a guest.
[sigh]
[clatter]
[Sound of footsteps moving away]
No, why don't you go to work?
Because the emergency board meeting is tomorrow
Well, as long as you avoid me until then.
Did you know it would be resolved?
What is a heliport?
What is Doctor Helicopter again?
No matter how much you do that
Emergency board meetings cannot be prevented.
A motion to cancel the appointment will be proposed tomorrow.
[Kang Hyuk] Director
So carelessly
[Chuckling] If you cut it off,
You will face public resistance.
[Jo Eun] The fact that it was an unfair parachute appointment
No change, yes?
The justification is sufficient.
Ah, director
I understand why you're doing this.
I really sincerely
I'm doing this for the patient.
No, I mean
At the Central Rescue Team
They said they would actively cooperate.
But why on earth!
no
That has limitations.
I have to go out at night too.
[laughter]
Are you going to run it 24 hours a day? huh?
Are you going to ruin our hospital?
at the board of directors
Would you agree, yes?
Oh, well, that's
Please only present the agenda.
Hey, man!
you!
What the hell is going on in our hospital?
What is your purpose?
- Why is it our hospital?
- [Tapping sound]
Maybe you're in trouble with Director Oh?
To ruin me
Is that so, huh?
[long breathing sound]
Reasons for coming to Korea University Hospital
[feeding]
Well, to tell you that
From why I became a doctor
Should I tell you?
[Joeun] What are you talking about?
[sigh]
[Sound of deep breathing]
yes
my father passed away
At that time, there was a serious accident
This hospital, that hospital
I didn't receive it anywhere
Well, I barely found it and went around and around.
At Korea University Hospital
He was declared dead.
that day
the doctor
I didn't give up till the end
Even though the golden time has passed
- [Beeping warning sound]
- [Doctor] Thirteen, fourteen, fifteen
- sixteen, seventeen, eighteen, nineteen
- [Emotional music]
Twenty, twenty-one, twenty-two, twenty-three...
Twenty-five, twenty... [Sound of strength]
[Continuous beeping sound]
[Kang Hyuk] I decided that day
I should become a doctor too
Like that person
I wanted to be a doctor like you.
24 years ago
like you
[Kanghyuk’s inhaling breath]
I did my best to save the patient.
Where is the doctor now?
[long breathing sound]
[Sound of deep breathing]
[Joeun’s long breathing sound]
[Emotional music fades out]
- [Yurim] Okay, everyone arrived, right? uh?
- [Sunwoo] Yes
- [click click]
- [Yurim] No, no
It's nice to take pictures
Don't get too close there
Because this is still new, right?
- Are all the reporters here? You came, right?
- [Sunwoo] Yes
[Yurim] Director, Eoyu, Director
- Oh my, oh my, director [laughter]
- [Jo Eun] Oh
[humorous music]
Maybe
Was it a gift from Professor Baek?
Director too?
[Awkward laughter]
[Joeun] Let’s laugh, uh
Don't be in a bad mood, okay?
[Joeun and Yurim’s exaggerated laughter]
[Myunghee] Yes, hello
[Yurim] Oh, over there
The Minister is also coming, this
[Myung-hee, Jo-eun, and Yu-rim’s laughter]
[Myunghee] You guys are here
[Joeun] Oh my, how can I travel such a long way?
How did you come this far?
can i fall in
[Joeun laughs along]
I can’t see Professor Baek.
- Oh, Professor Baek?
- Yes
Today's fall surgical conference
Because I have to attend
I went there
- You'll do well.
- [Yurim] Ah, yes
- Please take care of me.
- Yes, congratulations.
- Please sit down here, Minister.
- Please sit down.
[Myunghee] These are the clothes you two...
- I guess you guessed it, yeah.
- [Joeun] Yes, please sit down.
[Myunghee] Yes, hello
[Yurim] Welcome, welcome
[The humorous music stops]
[Kanghyuk’s microphone] Everyone
Why did you apply for surgery?
At the forefront of saving lives
Isn’t it because you want to stand?
But that front line
It's not just anywhere.
So
I came
- [Roaring roaring]
- [Interesting Music]
[Jaewon] Now, trauma surgery
This is an application, yes.
Here now
Will be working at a major trauma center
Improving the treatment of medical staff
Because it’s written down
- Please read carefully.
- [Kang Hyuk] Now, our teachers.
After rolling under me for 5 or 6 years,
second, third
It could be Baek Kang-hyuk
[Jaewon] Oh, and we
within 3 years
Severe trauma centers by local government
We plan to establish
- [Doctor 1] Is everything planned?
- [Interesting music stops]
There is no confirmation
[in a low voice] Mr. Lee…
[sigh]
[Jaewon’s tsk mouth sound]
Professor, let’s just quit.
Huh?
[Jaewon] Ah, these kids
I can't save people
At the trauma center, every minute and every second is urgent.
After hesitating like this, huh?
Don't miss a patient
[Roaring roar]
Go
Go! Oh, go, go!
[Doctor 2] I have a question.
[It becomes quiet]
[Jaewon] Huh?
uh!
uh! that…
south sudan
Seo, you’re Seo Dong-ju, right?
Go to a major trauma center
What happens?
- [Pisik]
- [Jaewon] Ah! Ah, if you look at this
- With this improvement in treatment…
- [Dongju] No
When I go to the trauma center, I
what can you do
That's what I'm asking
[Kang Hyuk] You can save people’s lives.
[Calm music]
Why our teachers became doctors
Wasn't that it?
ruler!
you can become a real doctor
The opportunity has come
First 50 people
[Roaring roar]
Nice to meet you
- No. 2
- [Soothing music fades]
No. 2?
- Uh
- [Magnificent music]
[Yurim Micro] Korea University Hospital
Severe trauma center doctor helicopter
From Agusta Westland, Italy
With a masterpiece created
- [click click]
- Stable even at night
For patients at any time
It is possible to go out
Now finally
At our Korea University Hospital,
State-of-the-art medical equipment and professional treatment…
[Jaewon] Sorry!
Sorry, I'm late!
[Jaewon’s heavy breathing]
[Majestic music heightens]
[click click]
[Yurim] Oh, welcome
Professor Baek, no.
[Welcome exclamation] Ah, there
Professor Baek Kang-hyuk is here, yes.
Who's the main character?
That's a disease
[Yurim] No, not yet
There's some left, there's some left
Wait a minute, let's go out, let's go out
[Rose] Teacher, but
What is that great person writing?
With Professor Baek’s permission,
Are you using it?
[Kyungwon] Permission?
No [mouths bitterly]
Just starting next week
Change the name and publish a web novel
I decided to get started
I'm anxious
[Kang Hyuk] Oh, hello.
This is Baek Kang-hyuk.
I usually come out like this
I hate it so much
Just these words
I feel like I have to give it to you.
What is a major trauma center?
Now, what is a major trauma center…
- [Mobile phone vibrating sound]
- [The majestic music fades]
sorry
[Yurim] Ah, I said, I said…
Yes, team leader
Yes, I'll be there right away.
[Yurim] Deployment?
Well, I don't think I need to explain much.
As you can see
This is a major trauma center.
Jaewon, let’s go.
- [Upbeat music]
- Yes, I understand.
- [Yurim] Are you dispatching?
- Let’s prepare the operating room.
- [Sunwoo] Where are you going? Gyeongwon-ah
- Teacher, let’s go.
[Yurim] Let’s go to the operating room quickly!
Oh, guys, there's an emergency right now.
I think it happened
Because the helicopter has to take off
Take your own chair and take refuge first.
- [Sunwoo] Put the mic away, mic
- [Yurim] Otherwise, everything will fly away.
[People's urgent voices]
Is it okay to fly the helicopter now, but?
[People keep making urgent noises]
I can float this, huh?
Did you do a safety check?
I don't know, I don't know...
[Kang Hyuk] Teacher Yang
Is it okay to take a helicopter now?
[Jaewon] Ah, Teacher Yang
It's a bit burdensome.
Just go for number 1.
Until there are 5 issues
[Kang Hyuk laughs] Really?
Then let's do it, anus
[Jaewon] Yes?
Boy, the anus is the starting point.
[Kang Hyuk’s bitter mouth sound]
First intention is always important, huh?
Anal, isn't it?
[Jaewon] I will do it, Mr. Yang, yes.
Teacher Yang, let’s go.
[Kanghyuk] Yes, Mr. Hang
Come on, let's go!
[The cheerful music stops]
[Calm music]